[{"answer": "Naughty - fertile, maybe, yes.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "(on camera) You're quite a naughty girl, aren't you, Vanessa?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "The title of the book originally came to me because I had gotten some interested about doing a memoir for years.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "What do I have no idea about?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, there was a large part that was fantastic and positive and overwhelming.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "What are you thinking when it all starts erupting like this?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Yes, partly.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Do you feel you achieved that goal?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "But there's no pressure, you know, when you're always underestimated -", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Do you feel like a little part of you has constantly been having to prove people wrong?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "ILLIAMS: Exactly.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Satisfying, too, isn't it?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Because I'm a rebel.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Why didn't you listen to your mum?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "You have no idea.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "You weren't quite what your teachers thought, were you?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "I loved Wilhelmina.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "That was a great part, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "ILLIAMS: I think so, wearing fabulous clothing and bossing people around.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "The stuff you dream of, isn't it?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Actually, we never had it.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "When did you have that conversation?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Read it, yes.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "So your mother read it?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "She didn't say anything.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "When your mother read it, what did she say to you?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "You haven't had any contact again?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Oh, I would say Broadway because he knew that that was my dream.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Of all the things that you did, what made him the proudest, do you think?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "We had a reception at my parents' house, and he just said that he was very proud and he knew that I accomplished a dream.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What did he say to you afterwards?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "No escaping.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Because there's no escaping, is there?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Do you think you would have had the platform to realize your dreams?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Oh, very stigmatized.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Were you slightly stigmatized by what happened?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I don't think slightly.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "My dad - I was in hiding.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "What did your dad say to you?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "You know, I knew my parents were there.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Why try and hide what's happened?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Was it any comfort to you that it was a massively successful publication, the Vanessa Williams nude pictures?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "It's getting sad.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, you've written about it.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "I've been through the same, so I know that that in the end is the glue, isn't it?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Oh, boy.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "How many times would you say you've been properly in love?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "And you married two of them?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Well, I do mention in the book that the two marriages that I ended up getting married to - I was pregnant both times that I got married.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "Or am I making an assumption there?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Naughty - fertile, maybe, yes.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "You're quite a naughty girl, aren't you, Vanessa?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "ILLIAMS: I have nothing going on in my life now, so I have nothing to be naughty about.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Have you matured fully, or are you still slightly naughty?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Yes, I would.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I went to his house.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "You did go out with Robert De Niro?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Is that the same thing?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Do you think it was ever going to be a Broadway thing out of that meeting?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Available and available for a relationship and not afraid of a relationship.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "If I could find for you now the perfect man based on all you've learned about love, romance, divorce, heartbreak, what would he be like?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Don't say you're 90.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Is 90 the word you're looking for?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I just wanted you to really want me.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Why have you been playing so hard to get?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I want you to kiss my chubby fingers in the way you just did in that clip.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "HITE: Yes?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "I happen to love what I do for a living.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "What motivates her to still do this?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "It's not magic.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "What is the Betty White magic?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Yes, mostly.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Are we still talking professional offers?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "I mean, do you still get men making inappropriate suggestions?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Well, actually, there is.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "Or is there something else that you don't understand?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Oh, it's probably like the rest of my wardrobe.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "And if so, how old is that top?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "Yes, well --", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Any nip and tuck ever gone on?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "Can you believe the way your life has gone, Betty?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "And in the middle of all that, there was the love of my life.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Crazy, eh?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "Oh, if that.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "I mean, they lasted a combined total of about three years, didn't they?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "Well, back in those days -- that's why people like Elizabeth Taylor are married so many times.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "But what was the reality of you and romantic life in those early days?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Did you really?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "As far as falling in love and being in love.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "Ever since that day have you ever even really looked at another man, or was that -- for you was that it?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "Allen Ludden.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "What is true love to you?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "It was his enthusiasm.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "What should women strive to get to to get the love you had?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "He would have been thrilled to pieces.", "docId": "120421pmt", "aSentId": 766, "question": "What would he have made of the way your career has just reached this extraordinary plateau?", "qSentId": 765}]